<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PHP on Tejiri Mayone</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/techs/php/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PHP on Tejiri Mayone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© copyright 2024</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:28:41 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/techs/php/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Samish Real Estate :Wordpress</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/samish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:28:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/samish/</guid>
      <description>Overview I had the privilege of developing a comprehensive website for Samish Real Estate Company, a leading construction company. This project involved implementing several advanced features to ensure the site is secure, functional, and user-friendly.&#xA;Features SSL Certification Security First: Implemented SSL certification to ensure all data transmitted between the user&amp;rsquo;s browser and the website is encrypted and secure. This not only protects user data but also builds trust with clients visiting the site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legislative Initiative For Sustainable Development :Wordpress</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/lisdel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 10:35:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/lisdel/</guid>
      <description>Description LISDEL Wordpress site, is a NGO website crafted with SEO excellence for optimal visibility. Navigate through captivating sliders and a stunning picture gallery, all seamlessly built with Elementor for a fluid, engaging user experience.&#xA;Key Features SEO Optimization: The site is fully optimized for search engines, ensuring higher visibility and better ranking on search results. This includes keyword integration, meta tags, and fast loading times.&#xA;Sliders: Dynamic sliders are integrated on the homepage and key landing pages, offering a visually stunning way to showcase featured content, promotions, and announcements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sterock Engineering Limited :Wordpress</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/sterockengineeringlimited/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 16:52:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/sterockengineeringlimited/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Sterock Engineering Limited is a leading construction company, and I had the privilege of developing their official website. This project was aimed at creating a secure, modern, and highly functional online presence that meets the company&amp;rsquo;s needs and enhances their digital footprint.&#xA;Key Features SSL Certificate To ensure the security and privacy of user data, I implemented an SSL certificate. This encrypts data transmitted between the users and the website, providing a secure browsing experience.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
